Jordon Moore

18 Draughton Street Bankfoot BD5 9QQ

Mobile: 07835178504

Email: Jordon.mooremoore@gmail.com

PROFILE

I am an enthusiastic, hardworking, determined and confident service desk analyst. I am experienced in a fast paced, customer focused technical support environment, passionate about IT and learning and I consider myself a fast learner, with a logical mindset. I enjoy resolving problems via troubleshooting and diagnosis. Others would consider me to be trustworthy, approachable, and respectful. I can easily adapt to the working environment, and can either work as a part of a team or by myself. I'm not afraid of challenging myself to excel in the tasks I do.

EDUCATION

Buttershaw Business & Enterprise College and Bradford College (2006-2013)

Qualifications	Level	Result
Functional Skills, English	2	Pass
Functional Skills, Maths	2	Pass
EdExcel BTEC IT	2	Pass
EdExcel BTEC Workskills	2	Pass

Baltic Training Apprenticeship (2013 – 2014)

Qualifications	Level	Result
Diploma in Occupational Competence, IT Professional	3	Pass
Diploma in Systems and Principles	3	Pass
MTA 98-366 Microsoft Technology Associate, Networking Fundamentals	2	Pass
Advanced Level Apprenticeship in I.T, Software, Web & Telecoms Professionals		Pass

SKILLS

- Operating System/Software/PC Installation, Configuration, Upgrades
- Troubleshooting basic and advanced issues
- PC and Network Security
- Data Protection and Backup
- Technical Fault Diagnosis and Fault Remedy
- Working with Hardware and ICT Equipment
- Networking Hardware and Cabling
- Network System Monitoring
- Wireless Networking Technologies
- IP Addressing
- Microsoft Office Skills including Microsoft Outlook, Word, PowerPoint and Excel

- Good Understanding of Various MSP's (Managed service platforms)
- Service Desk Ticketing Systems
- Excellent Telephone and Communication Skills
- Excellent Customer Support
- In depth attention to detail
- Creative and lateral thinking
- Strong punctuation
- Strong team player
- Router and Switch management
- Strong organizational skills
- Excellent relationship building
- Basic Apple configuration & troubleshooting
- Basic Linux configuration & troubleshooting

EMPLOYMENT AND WORK EXPERIENCE

Anchor Hanover Contractor

Service Desk Analyst - April 2019 - October 2019

Responsibilities

- Management of ticket queues and email pools
- Answered all calls within 2 minutes of a call queuing. Calls would typically peak over 300 per day.
- Dealing with any and all tickets for first time fix, pass over if 15 minutes had passed with no fix.
- Desk side support, if we couldn't fix an issue over the phone/remotely we would attend desk side in the building.
- Management of item acquisition and returns of work equipment went sent out to sites
- Understanding what the user needs and ordering all equipment necessary with installation and setup.
- Router and AP configuration when required. Setting static ip address, assigning printers to specific ips.
- Updating CMDB with all and current stock every Friday.
- Was apart of the windows 10 surface go roll out to 2000 users in the company.
- Support for all bespoke applications within the company.
- Provide alternative solutions. Was involved in weekly meetings on how to improve certain aspects of IT and how we can provide a better experience for our users.
- Supported the merge between Anchor and Hanover businesses putting in over time when asked/suggested.
- RDP/CMDB was used for the majority of remote support
- Every call that came through, whether deskside, email or phone call would be logged to ensure a full audit trail

Embed Health Consortium

Service Desk Analyst - 11th Nov 2017 - May 23rd

Responsibilities

- Management of daily emails submitted by the self service portal.
- Management of ticket queues Triage, Access management, Incident management and requests.
- Keeping to strict SLA and KPI guidelines.
- Assisting other members of staff with calls.
- Creation of knowledge base articles.

- Reporting new faults and fixes to the Team Leaders
- Use of remote connection tools such as Devolutions,RDP,CMRC
- Use of Jump servers to access Active directory and Exchange according to users base location.
- Use of Time Management and Keeping.
- Use of first time fix rates and being the 1st point of contact.
- Taking ownership of of new/progressing/resolved calls.
- Creation of Self Service portal accounts
- Use of active directory for change in permissions, groups, new users and leavers.
- Support and configuration of printers
- Support for the NHS clinical system; SystemOne, SystemOnline, Emis web
- Liaising with third parties for potential fixes; NHSmail, CBC Computers
- Installation and configuration of 3rd party tools and missing drivers; Java, .NET framework, PDF converter
- Management and ownership of Mass Incidents and Priority 1 calls.

Daisy Group

Service Desk Analyst – 3rd May 2016 – March 2017

Responsibilities

- Management of daily breach reports.
- Management of daily CMR (Customers requiring updates)
- Use of different ticketing portals such as; Service Now, AA10, Astea, Forcepoint Triton APX.
- Use of different monitoring platforms; Nimsoft, Stablenet and Supportbridge.
- Keeping on top of customer SLA's.
- Updating and inserting new data to knowledge bases; One note, CMDB and the Company WIKI.
- 1st point of contact for customer phone calls and tickets.
- Exchange account creation; Office 365, Microsoft exchange.
- Use of active directory for change in permissions, groups, new users and leavers.
- Creating directories and mapping drives.
- Brief use of Powershell.
- Use of remote access such as; CMRC, Bomgar, Lync and nRemote.

NHS Contractor BDCT (Bradford district care trust)

I.T Technician - 30th November 2015 - 6th January 2016

Responsibilities

- Answering phones to the districts users to help solve any issues they face.
- Configuring user profiles on several different applications such as, systmone, RIO, Footprints, Active directory.
- Using many methods of remote support such as, CmrC Viewer, Microsoft lync.
- Updating the current knowledgebase in one note.
- Mobile troubleshooting/setup and repairs.
- Monitoring the ticket queues 1st and 2nd line.
- Liaising with each team to help troubleshoot any issues that we faced.
- Setting up district email addresses through the NHSWeb Portal.

Working to strict deadlines.

Vit4u LTD Job Role

I.T Technician - October 2013 - March 2015

Responsibilities

- Scheduling, monitoring and checking the daily back-up and antivirus/Anti malware scans
- Monitoring the ticketing system for customer logged issues
- Communicating with customers, making outbound calls and responding to inbound calls
- Investigating, diagnosing and resolving issues
- Creating new user profiles and configuring permissions
- Proving remote technical support
- Offering technical advice and guidance to customers over the telephone
- Working to deadlines and completing tickets on time
- Resolving customer complaints
- Outbound sales, cold calling, promoting the business services
- Marketing, E-Marketing
- Using remote access to deal with user issues. (LogMein, Teamviewer and Kaseya)

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Online gaming with friends, studying hardware, software and the latest advancements within IT, home computing, repairs and upgrades. I consider myself to be a computer enthusiast and find myself using and reading about new technologies so I'm always up to date. Tinkering with hardware and software to gain a better understanding of how each device/application works.

References Available on Request